A Finding Aid to the Burt Chernow Papers, 1930-2002, in the Archives of American Art AAA.cherburt
Archives of American Art
- Research Material for Christo and Jeanne-Claude: A Biography, 1930-2002; Series 1; 17.1 Linear feet Boxes 1-17, 23, OV 24
  - Sound Recordings, 1977-1997; 1.2; 3 Linear feet Boxes 3-5
    - Interviews with Christo and Jeanne-Claude (Box 3)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1986 March 19; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 14, 13 (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 6)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1986 May 20; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 11, 12 (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 7)
      - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 1986 August 7; 1 Sound cassettes original, tape labeled 10; 1 Sound cassettes duplicate, tape labeled 185 (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 8)
      - Christo, 1986 September 26; 1 Sound cassettes duplicate, tape labeled 185; 1 Sound cassettes original, tape labeled 9 (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 9)
      - Christo and Jeanne-Claude on Bulgaria, 1986 November 28; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 8 (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 10)
      - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 1987 January 7; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 7, 6 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Jeanne Claude, 1987 February 5; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 20 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 2)
        Found on tape with Jeanne-Claude and Christo talking to students of the same date
      - Jeanne-Claude and Christo Talking to Students, 1987 February 5; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 20, 1 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 3)
        Part 1 found on same tape with Jeanne-Claude interview of the same date. The final part of Christo's talk is found in Interviews with Other Subjects, by Name, Lynn Hershman, 1987 February 14, tape 2 of 2.
      - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 1987 March 6; 3 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 5, 4, 3 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1987 March 11; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 23 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1987 March 27; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 2 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Christo, 1987 May 30; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 89 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 7)
      - Christo, 1987 August 19; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 22, 21 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 8)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1988 January 27; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 88 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 9)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1988 February 24; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 87 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 10)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1988 March 16; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 86 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 11)
      - Christo on Paris, 1988 July 21; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 84 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 12)
      - Jeanne-Claude on Paris, 1988 July 21; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 85 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 13)
        Found on same tape with Stefan Javacheff interview of the same date
      - Stefan Javacheff, 1988 July 21; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 85 (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 14)
        Found on tape with Jeanne-Claude interview of the same date
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1988 August 2; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 83 (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Christo on Vienna and Geneva, 1988 November 16; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 82, 81 (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1988 December 28; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 91 (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1989 February 2; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 80 (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Christo on Paris Years, 1989 July 18; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 79 (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Christo and Jeanne Claude, 1989 July 18; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 90 (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1989 December 26; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 78, 77 (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - Christo, 1990 January 25; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 75, 76 (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 8)
      - Christo, 1990 August 16; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 156, 155 (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 9)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1990 August 25; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 154 (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 10)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1991 June 14; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 153, and "JC, Christo, Ann Chernow, Harry Shunk, Moorehouse, Joyce, her daughter and boyfriend at Ecole" (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 11)
      - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 1991 November 21; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 74 (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 12)
      - Christo, 1991 December 10; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 73, 72 (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1992 March 5; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 152, 151 (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Jeanne-Claude Reviewing Pages 132-295, 1992 March 8; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 150 (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1962-1965 Questions, 1992 June 11; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 149, 148 (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - Christo, 1992 September 10; 2 Sound cassettes tapes numbered 147, 146 (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 5)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1992 October 25; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 145 (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 6)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1992 November 22; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 144 (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 7)
      - Christo, on 1963-1964, 1992 December 15; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 95 (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 8)
      - Jeanne-Claude Reviewing pages 297-398, 1992 December 29; 2 Sound cassettes tape labeled 94, 93 (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 9)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1993 April 15; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 142 (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 10)
      - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 1993 July 6; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 143, 267 (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 11)
      - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 1993 December 23; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 229 (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Jeanne Claude Reviewing Text, 1994 January 20; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 222, 223 (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1994 April 5; 3 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 228, 227, 226; and "mostly 1964 and 1965 with Christo at end" (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - Jeanne Claude, on 1966, 1994 September 14; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 141 (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 4)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1994 September 29; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 221; and "mostly mid-60s" (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 5)
      - Jeanne-Claude, on Australia, 1995 February 8; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 220 (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 6)
      - Jeanne-Claude, on Collaborating, 1995 February 13; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 219 (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 7)
      - Jeanne-Claude, Correcting Wrapped Coast Text, 1995 February 15; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 218, and "on her role as artist" (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 8)
      - Jeanne Claude, on Wrapped Staircase (1970), 1995 March 30; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 213 (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 9)
        Tape also contains brief comments on Umbrellas by artist Sam Weiner
      - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 1995 August 16; 3 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 212, 211, 210 (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 10)
      - Jeanne-Claude, Reviewing Pages 626-718, 1995 August 23; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 139 (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 11)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1995 November 17; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 140 (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 12)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1996 February 12; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 138, 137; and "Talking about book and Over the River" (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Jeanne-Claude Reviewing Pages 718-830, 1996 February 14; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 158, 157 (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Jeanne-Claude Reviewing Pages 831-886, 1996 April 12; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 209, 230 (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1996 April 28 (Box 3)
        Found on tape with Tom Golden interview of the same date, filed with Interviews with Other Subjects, by Name.
      - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 1996 May 13; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 231, 232 (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, on 1978, 1996 June 23; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 92, and "on 1978 Blind group in Kansas City and Munich Wrapped Floors" (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 5)
      - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, on Abu Dhabi, Rio, 1996 August 21; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 260, 261 (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 6)
      - Jeanne-Claude Reviewing Pages 887-950, 1996 August 22; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 200 (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 7)
      - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, on 1981, 1996 December 17; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 259, and "Wrapped Volvo, W. Brandt visit, Tokyo project, Leibowitz portrait" (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 8)
      - Jeanne-Claude Reviewing Pages 951-1002, 1996 December 19; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 258, and "on Bulgarian film on Christo and Anani" (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 9)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1997 January 10; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 255 (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 10)
      - Jeanne-Claude Reviewing Pages 1003-1032, 1997 March 2; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 257 (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 11)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1997 April 3; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 256 (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 12)
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1997 June; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 268, and "This is the last recorded phone call between Jeanne-Claude and Burt before he died." (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 13)
    - Interviews with Other Subjects, by Name (Box 4)
      - Pepe Jose Aceves, 1991 (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Umbrellas
      - Bob Adams, 1985 (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped
      - Karyn Allen, 1985 (Box 4)
      - Lawrence Alloway, 1986 March 7; 1 Linear feet taped labeled 178 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Ed Anderson on Running Fence, 1995 October 15; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 110 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Vahé Aprahamian, in Hitachi-Ota, Japan, 1991 October 9; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 162, 161 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 3)
        Part 2 found on same tape with interview with Berj Aprahamian of the same date. See also Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 24.
      - Berj Aprahamian, in Hitachi-Ota, Japan, 1991 October 9; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 161 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 4)
        Found on the same tape as part 2 of the Vahé Aprahamian interview of the same date.
      - Arman, 1987 September 3; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 245 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 5)
        Found on the same tape with part 1 of Arman interview dated 1991 October 24.
      - Arman, 1991 October 24; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 245, 244 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 6)
        Part 1 is found on the same tape with the Arman interview dated 1987 September 3.
      - Timothy Garton Ash, 1991 (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Wrapped Reichstag, 1995 June 21
      - Jacob Baal-Teshuva, 1991 May 15; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 170 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 5)
        See also Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 22-23; and Wrapped Reichstag, 1995 June 18-19.
      - Edith Bass, 1996 April 17; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 112, and "Rachel Karsenti's daughter" (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 6)
      - Mary Bauermeister, 1992 April 6; 3 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 251, 250, 249 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 7)
      - Mary Bauermeister, 1992 April 13; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 248 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 8)
      - Carline Bouilhet (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 26.
      - David Bourdon, 1985 September 26; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 282 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 9)
      - David Bourdon, 1994 April 14; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 180, 179 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 10)
      - Wolfgang Buggenhagen (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Wrapped Reichstag, 1995 June 21.
      - Toni Burringer (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 20.
      - Giovanni Camuffo, 1989 November 13; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 105 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 11)
      - Leo Castelli, 1986 March 7; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 102, and "Book excerpt then Castelli on Christo" (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 12)
      - Ann Chernow (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 19.
      - Leni Chevasson (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Wrapped Reichstag, 1995 June 17
      - Dale Chihuly (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Wrapped Reichstag, 1995 June 20.
      - Cyril Christo in Miami, 1983; 1 Sound cassettes original, tape labeled 66; 1 Sound cassettes duplicate, tape labeled 67 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 13)
      - Cyril Christo, 1996 January 5; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 24 (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Cyril Christo, 1996 January 22; 3 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 46, 48, 47 (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Bill Crimmins (Box 4)
      - Michael Cullen (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped (1985 September 19, 26, & 27), Umbrellas (1991 October 13), and Wrapped Reichstag (1995 June 18).
      - Jonita Davenport (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Wrapped Reichstag, 1995 June 17.
      - Serge DeBloe (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 21.
      - Suzanne Delehanty, 1987 March 10; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 104 (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Monica Dernhoff (Box 4)
      - Kathryn Donnelly (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Wrapped Reichstag, 1995 June 19.
      - Ted Dougherty, Lebec, California, 1991 October 13; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 165 (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 4)
        See also Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 22, 26, and 27.
      - Rosa Esman, 1987 May 26; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 100, and "at her gallery 70 Greene St." (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - Joe Fleming, on Surrounded Islands, 1997 March 1; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 115, also "Attorney" (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Carl Floch (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects, by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 25.
      - Jim Fuller (Box 4)
      - Thomas Garver (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Umbrellas, California, 1991 October 8.
      - John Gibson, 1995 January 10; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 118 (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 7)
      - Ellen Goheen, on Wrapped Walkways (1978), 1996 April 15; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 113 (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 8)
      - Tom Golden (Box 4)
        See also Ivan Karp, 1994 April 27, and Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped (1985 September 18).
        - In Lebec, California, 1991 October 12; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 167, 166 (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 9)
        - On the Reagan/Kohl Talk Related to Christo, 1995 August 18; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 106 (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 10)
        - On Rotterdam, 1977, 1996 April 28; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 96 (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 11)
          Also on tape is an interview with Jeanne-Claude of the same date.
      - Jeanne-Claude, 1996 April 28; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 96 (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 12)
        Found on cassette with Tom Golden interview of the same date.
      - Alexandra Gerard de Guillebon and Joyce-May Henery, 1995 February 24; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 45 (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 13)
      - Norbert de Guillebon, 1989 April 3; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 44 (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 14)
      - Precilda de Guillebon, 1987 April 16; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 40, 39 (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 15)
      - Precilda de Guillebon, 1990 December 21; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 38 (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Emil de Hantsetters (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 21.
      - Harrison Rivera-Terreaux (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 26.
      - Lynn Hershman, 1987 February 14; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 234, 233 (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 2)
        Final part of Christo's 1987 February 5 talk to students is found on tape 2 of this recording.
      - Christo Talk to Students, 1987 February 5; 1 Linear feet tape labeled 233 (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 3)
        Found on tape 2 of Lynn Hershman interview; part 1 of the 1987 February 5 Christo talk is filed with Interviews with Christo and Jeanne-Claude.
      - Joyce-May Henery, 1986 August 26; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 43, 42 (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Joyce-May Henery, 1989 November 6; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 41 (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Arnold Herstand, 1987 January 21; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 101, and "mostly Minnesota '66" (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Scott Hodes (Box 4)
      - Leslie Jackson (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Wrapped Reichstag, 1995 June 20.
      - Anani Javacheff (Box 4)
        - In Bulgaria, 1986 October 11-14; 7 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 35, 34, 33, 32, 31, 30, 29 (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 7)
        - With Didi and Vlado Javacheff, 1994 February 3; 2 Sound cassettes tapes 26, 25 (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 8)
        - With Vlado Translating for French Documentary Filmmakers, 1994 February 20; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 27 (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 9)
        - With Didi Javacheff and Jinka Langvad, 1996 November 14; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 36 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 1)
        - With Didi and Vlado Javacheff, on 1982, 1997 January 18; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 37 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Didi Javacheff (Box 4)
        See Anani Javacheff and Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Wrapped Reichstag, 1995 June 21.
      - Stefan Javacheff (Box 4)
        Interview found on the same tape as Interview with Jeanne-Claude dated 1988 July 21, filed with Interviews with Christo and Jeanne-Claude.
      - Paul Jenkins (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Others Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 27-28.
      - David Johnson (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 20.
      - Ray Johnson, 1990 April 14; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 240 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Ray Johnson, 1994 July 3; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 239 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - Annlee Juda (Box 4)
      - David Juda (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 23.
      - John Kaldor, 1995 June 17; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 129 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 5)
        See also Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 23.
      - Karen Kalish (Box 4)
      - Allan Kaprow, 1993 July 25; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 253 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 6)
      - Ivan Karp, 1994 April 27; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 265 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 7)
        Tape label also indicates additional content by Tom Golden. An additional interview with Karp is found on the cassette with an interview with Christo dated 1986 February 28.
      - Yolande Karsenti Medina, 1990 August 28; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 28 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 8)
      - Barbara Kayfetz, 1996 January 11; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 108 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 9)
      - Paul Kayfetz, 1996 January 13; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 111 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 10)
      - Ted Kheel Interviewed by Ann Chernow, 1991 October 10; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 171 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 11)
      - Fritz de Knegt (Box 4)
      - Josy Kraft (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 19.
      - Hilton Kramer, 1991 May 31; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 177 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 12)
      - Jivka Langvad, 1995 June 13; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 117 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 13)
        See also Anani Javacheff interview of 1996 November 14.
      - Hugh Levin, 1991 November 1; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 168 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 14)
      - Torsten Lilju (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 24.
      - Linde (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 25.
      - Albert Maysles (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped (1985 September 20), Umbrellas (1991 October 7), and Wrapped Reichstag (1995 June 20).
      - David Maysles (Box 4)
      - Dennis McCarthy (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Umbrellas, California, 1991 October.
      - Mary Fuller McChesney, 1996 January 2; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 266 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 15)
      - Ole Henrik Moe, 1995 June 17; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 126 (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 16)
      - Swana Morentz (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Wrapped Reichstag, 1995 June 20-21.
      - Priscilla Morgan, 1996 November 6; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 114 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Keiko Murata (Box 4)
      - Yusuke Nakahara (Box 4)
      - Howard Nemerovski on Running Fence (1976), 1995 October 11; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 109 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Annina Nosei, 1993 October 12; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 169 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - Lennart Preutz (Box 4)
      - Pierre Restany (Box 4)
        - In Paris, 1985 September 22; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 285 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 4)
        - In Hitachi-Ota, Japan, 1991 October 8; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 176 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 5)
        - In Lebec, California, 1991 October 13; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 175 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 6)
      - Larry Rivers, 1992 April 4; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 254 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 7)
      - Barbara Rose, 1994 September 28; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 183 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 8)
      - Klaus-Henning Rosen (Box 4)
      - Niki de Saint-Phalle, 1990 October 8; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 247 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 9)
      - Kauhiko Satani (Box 4)
      - Sabine Saphörster in Berlin, 1995 June 23; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 133 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 10)
      - Henry Scott-Stokes in Hitachi-Ota, Japan, 1991 October 8; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 163, 164 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 11)
      - George Segal, 1991 October 1; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 246 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 12)
      - Peter Selz, 1989 January 24; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 107 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 13)
      - Setsvko Shibata (Box 4)
        .See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Umbrellas, Japan, 1991 October 7
      - Harry Shunk, 1990 November 7; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 237, 238 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 14)
      - Harry Shunk, 1991 June 27; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 236 (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 15)
      - Holly Solomon, 1986 April 1; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 98 (Box 4, Folder 6, Item 1)
        See also Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 24, with Horace Solomon.
      - Ileana and Michael Sonnabend, 1991 May 14; 2 Sound cassettes tapes labeled 173, 174 (Box 4, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Katrin Specker (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Wrapped Reichstag, 1995 June 23.
      - Roland Specker (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Wrapped Reichstag, 1995 June 18.
      - Saul Steinberg, 1987 March 27; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 243, and "notes after interview" (Box 4, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - John Thompson (Box 4)
        See Interviews with Other Subjects by Project, Pont Neuf Wrapped, 1985 September 22.
      - John and Lucia Thompson, 1991 November 23; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 181 (Box 4, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Anita Thorhaug, 1997 March 16; 1 Sound cassettes tape labeled 116 (Box 4, Folder 6, Item 5)